Hello everyone, good morning.  So today I had to go to
a food tasting event
for which I was trying out outfits and I was loving
all of them.  Then finally
I wore this black one and I
ate a lot here because it was free and
so tasty.  After that I met a
cute dog who was very cute.
Then I came home and saw that another
parcel had arrived which was an invite
for another event and since it was an invite for the opening of a sweet shop, it contained a
lot of
namkeen and a lot of sweets and it contained
rasgullas but I was hoping it would be
gulab jamuns.  Then I
cleaned my face with Skin Vitamin C Face Wash
due to which my skin
texture already looked better and my skin
looked brighter.  After that, to moisturize my face,
I applied an even more advanced skin
brightening cream.  These products
are dermatologically tested and are
suitable for all skin types.  So this was
my simple two step skin care routine.
Then I went to Papa.  Then I went to my
sister's house where I met a cute
boy.  After that my sister gave me a lot of
chocolates which made me happy.
Then I brought it to my house and it
fell as soon as it entered the house.  Then I
ordered Ramen with her money and fed her, which made
her a little happy.  After that he
started colouring.  He forcibly made
me sit with him.  Then
mom prepared dinner which included kheer, potato
curry and spinach paneer.  Then I went to the gym.   That's
it.  Thank you so much for watching.  Do
like, share and subscribe.